Harold Stein Filk Collection
Harold Stein Filk Archive
- (So far) Unsorted Leftovers
  - Un-described Conventions
    - Counterpoint, Too / Grandman Went Out with a Bang / Featuring Leslie Fish / Tape 1 of 2, Notes: Origin: Convention: Counterpoint 2: 1996; Professional Cassette 1 copy (Box Box #24 (HH))
      Convention--Counterpoint 2: 1996; Professional Cassette
    - Counterpoint, Too / How Many of them Can We Made Die? / Featuring Heather Alexander / Tape 2 of 2, Notes: Origin: Convention: Counterpoint 2: 1996; Professional Cassette 1 copy (Box Box #24 (HH))
    - LosCon 42 "Don't Panic" hand towel, Notes: Origin: Convention: LosCon 42; copy (Box JW #22)
      Convention--LosCon 42
    - The North American Discworld Convention Baltimore Maryland 2013 Program Guide and Souvenir Book, Notes: Origin: Convention: North American Discworld Convention: 2013; Program book 2 copy (Box JW #22)
      Convention--North American Discworld Convention: 2013; Program book
    - Discworld Emporium, Notes: in the form of a humorous postcard Origin: Convention: North American Discworld Convention: 2013; Ad copy (Box JW #22)
      Convention--North American Discworld Convention: 2013; Ad
    - What does Terry Pratchett mean to you? Share your stories at terrypratchettappreciation.tumblr.com, Notes: received at North American Discworld Convention: 2013; enclosed in envelope from there Origin: Convention: North American Discworld Convention: 2013; Ad copy (Box JW #22)
    - NADWCon 2013 Pocket Program "BUT I DON'T HAVE POCKETS." Read Me, Notes: Origin: Convention: North American Discworld Convention: 2013; Pocket program copy (Box JW #22)
      Convention--North American Discworld Convention: 2013; Pocket program
    - Cloth bag, labeled "A Carrie from The Carpet People (C) Terry Pratchett", Notes: Origin: Convention: North American Discworld Convention: 2013; copy (Box JW #22)
      Convention--North American Discworld Convention: 2013
    - LosCon 39 schedule grid, Notes: Origin: Convention: LosCon 39; Schedule grid copy (Box JW #22)
      Convention--LosCon 39; Schedule grid
    - LosCon 38 schedule grid, Notes: Origin: Convention: LosCon 38; Schedule grid copy (Box JW #22)
      Convention--LosCon 38; Schedule grid
    - Conjecture 2012 schedule grid, Notes: Origin: Convention: Conjecture 2012; Schedule grid copy (Box JW #22)
      Convention--Conjecture 2012; Schedule grid
    - Loscon 40, Notes: Origin: Convention: LosCon 40; Program book copy (Box JW #22)
      Convention--LosCon 40; Program book
    - Westercon 63 / ConChord 23, Notes: also includes various other associated papers (schedule grid, etc.) Origin: Convention: ConChord 23; Program book copy (Box JW #22)
      Convention--ConChord 23; Program book
    - ConChords and Choruses: ConChord #23 and Westercon #63 (2010), Notes: Origin: Convention: ConChord 23; Songbook copy (Box JW Blue suitcase)
      Convention--ConChord 23; Songbook
    - VCON 40, Notes: with copy of "Why You Got This Zine #7" inside Origin: Convention: VCON 40; Program book copy (Box JW #22)
      Convention--VCON 40; Program book
    - Norwescon 39, Notes: Origin: Convention: Norwescon XXXIX; Program book copy (Box JW #22)
      Convention--Norwescon XXXIX; Program book
    - Norwescon 39 Pocket Program Planning & Membership Guide, Notes: Origin: Convention: Norwescon XXXIX; Pocket program copy (Box JW #22)
      Convention--Norwescon XXXIX; Pocket program
    - Loscon 41, Notes: including schedule grid & "Neverwhere" themed party advert Origin: Convention: Loscon 41; Program book copy (Box JW #22)
      Convention--Loscon 41; Program book
    - Loscon 41 schedule grid, Notes: Origin: Convention: Loscon 41; Schedule grid copy (Box JW #22)
      Convention--Loscon 41; Schedule grid
    - Norwescon 38, Notes: including perfume ad & voter registration form Origin: Convention: Norwescon XXXVIII; Program book copy (Box JW #22)
      Convention--Norwescon XXXVIII; Program book
    - Pocket Program Saturday and Sunday Programming Norwescon 38, Notes: Origin: Convention: Norwescon XXXVIII; Pocket program copy (Box JW #22)
      Convention--Norwescon XXXVIII; Pocket program
    - Pocket Program Thursday and Friday Programming Norwescon 38, Notes: Origin: Convention: Norwescon XXXVIII; Pocket program copy (Box JW #22)
    - Pocket Program Planning and Membership Guidelines Norwescon 38, Notes: Origin: Convention: Norwescon XXXVIII; Pocket program copy (Box JW #22)
    - Westercon 68 Program Book, Notes: Origin: Convention: Westercon 68; Program book 2 copy (Box JW #22)
      Convention--Westercon 68; Program book
    - Westercon 68 Progress Report 2, Notes: Origin: Convention: Westercon 68; Progress report copy (Box JW #22)
      Convention--Westercon 68; Progress report
    - News Horizon Westercon 68 7/3/2015, Notes: Origin: Convention: Westercon 68; Newsletter copy (Box JW #22)
      Convention--Westercon 68; Newsletter
    - Westercon 68 Schedule Grid LARGE PRINT, Notes: Origin: Convention: Westercon 68; Schedule grid copy (Box JW #22)
      Convention--Westercon 68; Schedule grid
    - Epic Horizons Daily Zine for Norwescon 38 Saturday, April 4, 2015, Notes: Origin: Convention: Norwescon 38; Newsletter copy (Box JW #22)
      Convention--Norwescon 38; Newsletter
    - 6 Munchkin promo cards received at LosCon 2012, Notes: Origin: Convention: LosCon 2012; Game cards copy (Box JW #22)
      Convention--LosCon 2012; Game cards
    - Conflikt 13, Notes: Origin: Convention: Conflikt 13; Program booklet copy (Box JW #22)
      Convention--Conflikt 13; Program booklet
    - Conflikt 13, Notes: Origin: Convention: Conflikt 13; Program booklet copy (Box JW Blue suitcase)
    - Conflikt 13 Songbook, Notes: in orange cover with no label Origin: Convention: Conflikt 13; Songbook copy (Box JW Blue suitcase)
      Convention--Conflikt 13; Songbook
    - Norwescon 39 Pocket Program Saturday & Sunday, Notes: Origin: Convention: Norwescon 39; Pocket program copy (Box JW #22)
      Convention--Norwescon 39; Pocket program
    - Norwescon 39 Pocket Program Thrusday & Friday, Notes: Origin: Convention: Norwescon 39; Pocket program copy (Box JW #22)
    - Ad for Neon Galaxy 2014, Notes: in a plastic bag, includes two fliers, a business card from a travel agent, and two tourist pamphlets about Nevada Origin: Convention: Neon Galaxy 2014; Ad copy (Box JW #22)
      Convention--Neon Galaxy 2014; Ad
    - Loscon 42 postcard ad, Notes: Origin: Convention: Loscon 42; Ad copy (Box JW #22)
      Convention--Loscon 42; Ad
    - Loscon 40 Pocket Program, Notes: even though it's titled "Pocket Program" it's actually a schedule grid, but in large font Origin: Convention: Loscon 40; Schedule grid copy (Box JW #22)
      Convention--Loscon 40; Schedule grid
    - Loscon 44 Program, Notes: Origin: Convention: Loscon 44; Pocket program copy (Box JW #22)
      Convention--Loscon 44; Pocket program
    - Conjecture 2012 & ConChord 24, Notes: Origin: Convention: ConChord 24; Program booklet copy (Box JW #22)
      Convention--ConChord 24; Program booklet
    - Conjecture 2010, Notes: Origin: Convention: Conjecture 2010; Program booklet copy (Box JW #22)
      Convention--Conjecture 2010; Program booklet
    - Loscon 37, Notes: Origin: Convention: Loscon 37; Program booklet copy (Box JW #22)
      Convention--Loscon 37; Program booklet
    - Loscon 37 Sunday [partial], Notes: Origin: Convention: Loscon 37; Schedule grid copy (Box JW #22)
      Convention--Loscon 37; Schedule grid
    - Loscon 38, Notes: Origin: Convention: Loscon 38; Program booklet copy (Box JW #22)
      Convention--Loscon 38; Program booklet
    - Loscon 39, Notes: Origin: Convention: Loscon 39; Program booklet copy (Box JW #22)
      Convention--Loscon 39; Program booklet
    - Condor XX, Notes: Origin: Convention: Condor XX; Program booklet copy (Box JW #22)
      Convention--Condor XX; Program booklet
    - Condor XXI, Notes: Origin: Convention: Condor XXI; Program booklet copy (Box JW #22)
      Convention--Condor XXI; Program booklet
    - A Martian Holiday Gaslight Gathering 4, Notes: Origin: Convention: Gaslight Gathering 4; Program booklet copy (Box JW #22)
      Convention--Gaslight Gathering 4; Program booklet
    - Conflikt X, Notes: includes schedule grid Origin: Convention: Conflikt X; Program booklet copy (Box JW #22)
      Convention--Conflikt X; Program booklet
    - Conflikt 12, Notes: Origin: Convention: Conflikt 12; Program booklet copy (Box JW #22)
      Convention--Conflikt 12; Program booklet
    - Conflikt 12 Songbook, Notes: in blue cover with no label Origin: Convention: Conflikt 12; Songbook copy (Box JW Blue suitcase)
      Convention--Conflikt 12; Songbook
    - Maritime Songs and Filk Songs, Notes: from Loscon 46 theme circle on Saturday evening Origin: Convention: Loscon 46; Songbook copy (Box JW Blue suitcase)
      Gold, Lee; Convention--Loscon 46; Songbook
    - Poul & Karen Anderson Memorial Songbook, Notes: Origin: Convention: Loscon 2018; Songbook copy (Box JW Blue suitcase)
      Gold, Lee; Convention--Loscon 2018; Songbook
    - GAFilk 2020 Songbook, Notes: Origin: Convention: GAFilk 2020; Songbook copy (Box JW Blue suitcase)
      Convention--GAFilk 2020; Songbook
    - Con Chords and Choruses: The City of Tomorrow, Circa 1947 A.D., Notes: Origin: Convention: ConChord 13: 1998; Songbook copy (Box JW Blue suitcase)
      Convention--ConChord 13: 1998; Songbook
    - ConChords and Choruses: ConChord #16 (2002), Notes: Origin: Convention: ConChord 16; Songbook copy (Box JW Blue suitcase)
      Convention--ConChord 16; Songbook
    - ConChords and Choruses Addendum [#21 2008], Notes: Origin: Convention: ConChord 21: 2008; Songbook copy (Box JW Blue suitcase)
      Convention--ConChord 21: 2008; Songbook
    - ConChords and Choruses: ConChord #17 (2003), Notes: Origin: Convention: ConChord 17; Songbook copy (Box JW Blue suitcase)
      Convention--ConChord 17; Songbook
    - ConChords and Choruses: ConChord #22 (2009), Notes: Origin: Convention: ConChord 22; Songbook copy (Box JW Blue suitcase)
      Convention--ConChord 22; Songbook
    - 2001 a filk oddity con-chord 15, aug. 10-12, Notes: Origin: Convention: ConChord 15; Songbook copy (Box JW Blue suitcase)
      Convention--ConChord 15; Songbook
    - ConChords and Choruses: ConChord #20 (2007), Notes: Origin: Convention: ConChord 20; Songbook copy (Box JW Blue suitcase)
      Convention--ConChord 20; Songbook
  - Non-Audio Unsorted Stuff
    - Cold Iron - Featuring the songs of Leslie Fish, 1987; Notes: OCP-14B: A pristine copy of this classic songbook with illustrations by Brad Schenk Origin: Off Centaur Publications, 1987; Songbook 2 copy; Fish, Leslie and Kipling, Rudyard; Off Centaur Publications, 1987 (Box Box #02 (FF))
      Fish, Leslie and Kipling, Rudyard; Fish, Leslie and Kipling, Rudyard; Off Centaur Publications, 1987; Off Centaur Publications, 1987; Songbook
    - Some Filk Terms Every Fan Should Know, Notes: This is a crammed sheet of paper with definitions for filk in jokes, like Frank Hayes Disease, Microfilk (also a Filthy Pierre creation), and descriptions of how filk circles are conducted. On the back, crammed together is a directory for microfilk as a PDF that gives an address to access it on Harold's domain, floatingfilk.com/mp3/microfilk.pdf. Origin: Distributed by Filthy Pierre at an east coast filk convention.; Lexicon 1 copy; Strauss, Erwin S aka Filthy Pierre (Box Box #02 (FF))
      Strauss, Erwin S aka Filthy Pierre; Strauss, Erwin S aka Filthy Pierre; Distributed by Filthy Pierre at an east coast filk convention.; Lexicon
    - APA-Filk #55, 1 Aug, 1992, 1 August 1992; Notes: White covered APA with angels playing instruments. Origin: Boardman, John; APA 2 copy; Boardman, John (Box Box #02 (FF))
      Boardman, John; APA-Filk; Boardman, John; APA
    - APA-Filk #63, Aug, 1994, 1 August 1994; Notes: Yellow covered APA with a pigeon in a suit, smoking an olive branch on a mountain. Origin: Boardman, John; APA 1 copy; Boardman, John (Box Box #02 (FF))
    - APA-Filk #62, May 1994, 1 May 1994; Notes: Blue covered APA with a picutre of the Beatles. Origin: Boardman, John; APA 1 copy; Boardman, John (Box Box #02 (FF))
    - APA-Filk #60, May 1993, 1 May 1993; Notes: Comic covered APA with some pages printed on pink paper and a half width insert ad for Science Fiction Mysteries and More (a defunct bookstore that was popular in NYC fandom). Origin: Boardman, John; APA 1 copy; Boardman, John (Box Box #02 (FF))
    - APA-Filk #61, Feb 1994, 1 February 1994; Notes: Pink covered APA with a cartoon of Barney the Dinosaur holding money and singing - 15th Anniversary issue. Origin: Boardman, John; APA 1 copy; Boardman, John (Box Box #02 (FF))
    - APA-Filk #59, 1 Aug, 1993, 1 August 1993; Notes: Comic covered APA Origin: Boardman, John; APA 1 copy; Boardman, John (Box Box #02 (FF))
    - APA-Filk #58, 1 May 1993, Notes: Comic covered APA with some pages printed on light blue or bright blue paper. Origin: Boardman, John; APA 1 copy; Boardman, John (Box Box #02 (FF))
    - APA-Filk #57, 1 February 1993, Notes: Comic covered APA with some pink pages Origin: Boardman, John; APA 1 copy; Boardman, John (Box Box #02 (FF))
    - APA-Filk #54, 1 May, 1992, Notes: Comic covered APA with a ballot on the back Origin: Boardman, John; APA 1 copy; Boardman, John (Box Box #02 (FF))
    - APA-Filk #53, 1 February 1992, 13th Anniversary, Notes: Comic covered APA, with blue pages in back. Origin: Boardman, John; APA 1 copy; Boardman, John (Box Box #02 (FF))
    - APA-Filk #51, November, 1991, Notes: White covered APA with Family Circus cartoon Origin: Boardman, John; APA 1 copy; Boardman, John (Box Box #02 (FF))
    - APA-Filk #41, February 1989, Notes: White covered APA with a cartoon of the number ten with filksongs falling out of it in a stream. There's also a reprint of the first lines of Happy birthday with a cease and desist. Origin: Boardman, John; APA 1 copy; Boardman, John (Box Box #02 (FF))
    - APA-Filk #45, February 1990, 1 February 1990; Notes: Comic covered APA Origin: Boardman, John; APA 2 copy; Boardman, John (Box Box #02 (FF))
    - APA-Filk #43 - No date listed, Notes: White covered APA with spirograph style drawings Origin: Boardman, John; APA 1 copy; Boardman, John (Box Box #02 (FF))
    - Original advertising poster for Sourcery by Terry Pratchett - possibly from Science Fiction Mysteries and More, Notes: Poster for Terry Pratchett's Sourcery with insert posters for The Light Fantastic, The Colour of Magic, Equal Rites and Mort Origin: Science Fiction, Mysteries and More (Bookstore); Poster 1 copy; Kirby (Box Box #02 (FF))
      Kirby; Kirby; Science Fiction, Mysteries and More (Bookstore); Poster
    - Erwin S. (Filthy Pierre) Strauss' O*F*F*I*C*I*A*L CAMP LUNACON SINGALONG, Notes: A one-sheet listing songs to be sung at a programming item at a Lunacon. Origin: Distributed by Filthy Pierre at a Lunacon (year unknown); Songsheet 1 copy; Strauss, Erwin S aka Filthy Pierre (Box Box #02 (FF))
      Strauss, Erwin S aka Filthy Pierre; Strauss, Erwin S aka Filthy Pierre; Distributed by Filthy Pierre at a Lunacon (year unknown); Songsheet
    - APA-Filk #50, May 1, 1991, 1 May 1991; Notes: Comic covered APA Origin: Boardman, John; APA 1 copy; Boardman, John (Box Box #02 (FF))
    - APA-Filk #51, August 1, 1991, 1 August 1991; Notes: Comic covered APA, the numbering seems to duplicate an issue from later in the year that also claims to be #51 Origin: Boardman, John; APA 1 copy; Boardman, John (Box Box #02 (FF))
    - APA-Filk #39, August 1988, 1 August 1988; Notes: White colored APA with Far Side Cartoons, and a joke about Worldcon in New Orleans Origin: Boardman, John; APA 1 copy; Boardman, John (Box Box #02 (FF))
    - APA-Filk #38, May 1, 1988, 1 May 1988; Notes: Comic covered APA Origin: Boardman, John; APA 1 copy; Boardman, John (Box Box #02 (FF))
    - APA-Filk #37, February 1988, 1 February 1988; Notes: White covred APA with a comic of the world as a vinyl record Origin: Boardman, John; APA 1 copy; Boardman, John (Box Box #02 (FF))
    - APA-Filk #34, May 1, 1987, 1 May 1987; Notes: Comic covered APA with internal blue pages Origin: Boardman, John; APA 1 copy; Boardman, John (Box Box #02 (FF))
    - APA-Filk #40, November 1, 1988, 1 November 1988; Notes: Comic covered APA with interior pages in blue Origin: Boardman, John; APA 1 copy; Boardman, John (Box Box #02 (FF))
    - APA-Filk #44, November 1989, 1 November 1989; Notes: White covered APA with a comic about the San Francisco earthquake Origin: Boardman, John; APA 1 copy; Boardman, John (Box Box #02 (FF))
    - APA-Filk #42, 1 May 1989, Notes: Light green covered APA with a cartoon of Zaphod Beeblebrox as a two headed George Washington Origin: Boardman, John; APA 1 copy; Boardman, John (Box Box #02 (FF))
    - APA-Filk #47, 12 July 1990, Notes: Pink covered double APA - includes APA-Q # 319 Origin: Boardman, John; APA 1 copy; Boardman, John (Box Box #02 (FF))
    - APA-Filk #46, 1 May 1990, Notes: Pink covered issue with Anakreon on the front page (unusual) Origin: Boardman, John; APA 1 copy; Boardman, John (Box Box #02 (FF))
    - APA-Filk #49, 1 February 1991, Notes: White covered issue with Groucho Marx and Harpo Marx cartoon about war. Origin: Boardman, John; APA 1 copy; Boardman, John (Box Box #02 (FF))
    - APA-Filk #48, 1 November 1990, Notes: Comic covered issue with Christmas themes Origin: Boardman, John; APA 1 copy; Boardman, John (Box Box #02 (FF))
    - APA-Filk #68, November 1995, 1 November 1995; Notes: White issues with a smashed guitar, this appears to have been the last issue. Origin: Boardman, John; APA 1 copy; Boardman, John (Box Box #02 (FF))
    - APA-Filk #66, 1 May 1995, Notes: Comic covered issue with Anakreon label Origin: Boardman, John; APA 1 copy; Boardman, John (Box Box #02 (FF))
    - APA-Filk #66, May 1995 - In Memoriam, 1 May 1995; Notes: White covered issue with a cartoon of a mushroom cloud and a kazoo Origin: Boardman, John; APA 1 copy; Boardman, John (Box Box #02 (FF))
    - APA-Filk #65, February 1995, 1 February 1995; Notes: White covered issue with Betty Boop cartoon Origin: Boardman, John; APA 1 copy; Boardman, John (Box Box #02 (FF))
    - Swapped Out Songs, Notes: White cover with pictures of computers making noises with stars and lightning. Origin: Osband, Robert, via OZ Press; Songbook 1 copy; Osband, Robert, via OZ Press; OZ Press (Box Box #02 (FF))
      Osband, Robert, via OZ Press; Various; Osband, Robert, via OZ Press; OZ Press; Songbook
    - The New York Conspiracy Hymnal, Notes: White cover with Q-Bert or someone like him playing the piano while smoking a cigar Origin: Costikyan, Greg; Songbook 1 copy; Costikyan, Greg (Box Box #02 (FF))
      Costikyan, Greg; Various; Costikyan, Greg; Songbook
    - Musical Chas - A filksong fanzine Vol 2. Number 2, Notes: This appears to have originated with The Capitol Hill Area Science Fiction and Narcissism Society Origin: CHASFANS; Fanzine / Songbook 1 copy; CHASFANS (Box Box #02 (FF))
      CHASFANS; Various; CHASFANS; Fanzine / Songbook
    - Musical Chas - A filksong fanzine vol 1 no 1, Notes: This appears to have originated with The Capitol Hill Area Science Fiction and Narcissism Society Origin: CHASFANS; Fanzine / Songbook 1 copy; CHASFANS (Box Box #02 (FF))
    - Musical Chas - Last issue, Notes: This appears to have originated with The Capitol Hill Area Science Fiction and Narcissism Society Origin: CHASFANS; Fanzine / Songbook 1 copy; CHASFANS (Box Box #02 (FF))
    - "They Don't Write 'Em Like That ... Yet" Volume one, Notes: White covered songbook with various strange animals and musical instruments Origin: Higgins, Bill and Skirvin, Mary Lynn; Songbook 1 copy; Higgins, Bill and Skirvin, Mary Lynn (Box Box #02 (FF))
      Higgins, Bill and Skirvin, Mary Lynn; Various; Higgins, Bill and Skirvin, Mary Lynn; Songbook
    - Rec-Room Rhymes Omnibus, Notes: Sepia cover with fancy printing Origin: Rogow, Roberta; Songbook 1 copy; Rogow, Roberta (Box Box #02 (FF))
      Rogow, Roberta; Rogow, Roberta; Rogow, Roberta; Songbook
    - FAN-tastic Filk Songs and other Fannish Delights, July-September Vol 1. No. 1, Notes: Glossy cover with spaceship and a fan swimming in space Origin: Gerds, Eric; Fanzine / Songbook 1 copy; Gerds, Eric (Box Box #02 (FF))
      Gerds, Eric; Various; Gerds, Eric; Fanzine / Songbook
    - The Starships - lyric: Glen T. Cox, tune; Jim Little, 1979, Notes: Sheet music on very damaged paper. Side two has The Title Will Follow by Bill Roper and Clif Flynt Origin: Cox, Glen T. and Little, Jim; Songsheet 1 copy; Cox, Glen T. and Little, Jim (Box Box #02 (FF))
      Cox, Glen T. and Little, Jim; Various; Cox, Glen T. and Little, Jim; Songsheet
    - Tin Soldiers - lyric: Michele Cox, based on the story by Joan D. Vinge tune: Veni Immanuel/O Come O Come Immanuel on the other side of the lyrics of The Title Will Follow, Notes: Sheet music on one side, lyrics on the other side for The Lyrics Will Follow Origin: Cox, Michele; Songsheet 1 copy; Cox Michele (Box Box #02 (FF))
      Cox Michele; Various; Cox, Michele; Songsheet
    - Captain Marvel Culture.com, Notes: Half page of a promotoin for a book and video project being promoted by a filker Origin: Zorikh; Pamphlet 1 copy; Lequidre, Zorikh, and Azriliant, Evan (Box Box #02 (FF))
      Lequidre, Zorikh, and Azriliant, Evan; Lequidre, Zorikh, and Azriliant, Evan; Zorikh; Pamphlet
    - Musical Mayhem by P.F. Bruns, Notes: Green cover with lots of circles Origin: Bruns, P.F.; Songbook 1 copy; Bruns, P.F. (Box Box #02 (FF))
      Bruns, P.F.; Bruns, P.F.; Bruns, P.F.; Songbook
    - The Star Spangled Filkbook, Notes: Patriotic historical filk Origin:; Songbook 1 copy (Box Box #02 (FF))
      NA; Songbook
    - An Even Scarier Solistice, 2006; Notes: Light green booklet with lyrics Origin: H.P. Lovecraft Historical Society; Songbook 1 copy; H.P. Lovecraft Historical Society (Box Box #02 (FF))
      H.P. Lovecraft Historical Society; H.P. Lovecraft Historical Society; Songbook
    - Let's Filk About #3, 1994; Notes: Light grey cover with fire lizards Origin:; Fanzine / Songbook 1 copy (Box Box #02 (FF))
      Various; Fanzine / Songbook
    - Arise My Love/Dark Memories, 1981; Notes: Double sided sheet music Origin:; Sheet music 1 copy; McQuillan, Cynthia (Box Box #02 (FF))
      McQuillan, Cynthia; McQuillan, Cynthia; Sheet music
    - Ryan's Star/Lycanthropy, Notes: Double sided sheet music Origin: Singer in the Shadow (possibly from a songbook); Sheet music 1 copy; McQuillan, Cynthia; Singer in the Shadow (possibly from a songbook) (Box Box #02 (FF))
      McQuillan, Cynthia; Singer in the Shadow (possibly from a songbook); McQuillan, Cynthia; Singer in the Shadow (possibly from a songbook); Sheet music
    - DNA Boogie/undentified (possibly more lyrics and an illo), Notes: Double sided sheet music Origin: Singer in the Shadow (possibly from a songbook); Sheet music 1 copy; McQuillan, Cynthia; Singer in the Shadow (possibly from a songbook) (Box Box #02 (FF))
    - Possibly a schedule from ConChord, unknown year., Notes: White, single sided Origin: ConChord, unknown year; Schedule grid 1 copy; ConChord, unknown year (Box Box #02 (FF))
      ConChord, unknown year; NA; ConChord, unknown year; Schedule grid
    - Map of Setac, Notes: Map of Setac area, possibly from a Conflikt or a Seattle worldcon? Origin:; Map 1 copy (Box Box #02 (FF))
      NA; Map
    - OVFF Song Writing Contest Audience Choice Ballot, Notes: No year printed on ballot. Ballot is unused Origin: OVFF (unknown year); Ballot 1 copy; OVFF (unknown year) (Box Box #02 (FF))
      OVFF (unknown year); NA; OVFF (unknown year); Ballot
    - Handwritten note from unknown signature probably about the Consonance materials, Notes: Green ink on white index card Origin:; Note 1 copy (Box Box #02 (FF))
      Note